

GILBERT JOSE

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JavaScript
React
Firebase
HTML5, CSS3
Responsive Design
Sass
JavaScript tooling with Gulp
Git and GitHub
Visual Studio Code
Website Accessibility

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team player
Self-motivated
Courteous and conscientious
Organized
Time management
Driven to learn and grow

CONTACT

P: 416-275-8784 E: code@gilbertjose.ca W: www.gilbertjose.ca

SOCIAL



linkedin.com/in/gilbertjose



github.com/bet-code



@gilbert_j5

ABOUT

I am a passionate web developer and technology enthusiast with over 10 years of professional IT technical support and customer service experience in a telecommunication environment. I am a keen student of web development, consciously finding every opportunity to expand and master my craft. I look forward to solving complex issues and work in a team of talented coders.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TECHXPERT TECHNICAL SUPPORT

Rogers Communication | Jun 2011 - Jul 2016

- Resolve complex technical issues such as PC optimization, virus eradication, data recovery, network connectivity etc.
- Provide support on wide range of Operating Systems such as iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows and Mac
- Setup and configure home networking devices, such as home routers, wireless printers, security cameras etc.
- Problem solve with emphasis on fixing root cause.

WIRELESS LIVE CHAT TECHNICAL SUPPORT Rogers Communication | Sep 2009 - Jun 2011

- Utilize vendor's software and tools to identify and support issues such as software incompatibility, data synchronization, backup and OS re-install.
- Diagnose and troubleshoot mobile network connectivity.
- Configure and troubleshoot mobile OS settings, email and device features.

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELPMENT IMMERSIVE CERTIFICATE

HackerYou College of Technology | Jan 2017- Dec 2017

COMPUTER SYSTEM AND NETWORKING Xintra College | 2002 - 2003